《I Will Never Give Up》
我的生命从不为谁后悔
陪你浪漫燃烧直到熄灭
珍惜生命中的每次眼泪
有天我会勇敢不再更变
而我盲目的追 低头妥协
想保护着谁
我想许愿 拥有你的明天
我只想在我一边
每天都能将面对
生命总会有机会
而你准备要浪费
在我一边
优优独播剧场——YoYo Television Series Exclusive
中文字幕组
老师,等我们啊
糟糕了
看起来很惨
他都不读不回啊
让我塑胶
你不是知道他在哪里工作吗
可是我不敢面对他
为什么
他一定最有心的小屁孩一个
连你都不理我
你是啊
好嘛
我本来想说直接去找他
他可能又被打枪
他说连朋友都当不成
这次我真的不敢
天生你的Uber Eats来咯
也太快了吧
有没有
为什么有披萨
当然好啊
等一下
我不是叫六个鸡腿便当吗
为什么只有四个
我
你不知道我相递一天要吃六只鸡腿
才会溜溜溜溜溜吗
我们鸡腿的部分目前断货
没有关系
我们邀请到了人人歐爸
高小群
来为你做一对一的喂食
喂他
不好意思
我们现在为你做一个喂食的动作
是的
小可怜让我喂你吃
你们这很北蓝
怎么样这样的服务满意吗
满意给两百
外加五颗星
三小啦
高小群配平他啦
好好
你要上哪里啊
他最近干嘛啊想要这样
不好
小安
有
阿豪呢
他昨天中午都没跟我们一起啊
他不是去找你吗
他没有跟你在一起
那他会在哪
我怎么会知道
孙博翔
你一定知道他在哪
你要找他你自己打电话给他
问我干嘛
你们很废
问我
你在哪
学校
我帮你做你在学校
最高可达五万倍十万倍
下一位幸运儿就是你
阿豪
我在忙啊
你怎么了
你忘记我们要一起去吃午饭
我现在不饿
不是要不饿的问题
是我们
我先忙
拜拜
下楼听快点电话
他应该有急事啦
是吗
他去厕所
家一
他在擦屁股
没时间讲啦
就是这样
一定是这样
有什么样老大就有什么样的猴子啦
老大
猴子
猴子在吗
我现在都过一半了还是谁
家一
猴子在吗
猪包包
猴子在嗎
猴子在吗
猴子要上厕所
ice
pervert
Wang Zhuo
You!
Let me!
You're still eating?
I'll buy you some drinks.
What's up?
Why did you hang up on me?
You couldn't find anyone this afternoon.
I'm busy.
Busy about what?
You said you wanted to discuss the Han family matter.
I already said it.
I just want to make a decision with you.
Don't I have any opinion?
Why is it always me who decides?
You only made it so that I want to go and you don't want to go.
I'm not going to go.
I'm going to go.
Did I say I like Yu Xi Gu
and you didn't want to talk to me?
I already apologized to you.
Didn't we make up?
I didn't mean to ignore you.
Don't think about it.
Let's discuss it together.
Next.
I'm leaving.
Bye.
What do I have to do to make up?
I'm sorry.
The exam is very important to me.
If you want me to apologize, I'm willing to.
I don't understand what you're saying.
You say you want to hear it.
Then tell me the result.
It's so cool to eat.
Take a bite.
Want to order it yourself?
Let go of that cake.
That cake.
The exam is very important to me.
You can ask her to apologize.
She can do it.
So you're still looking for Yu Xi Gu?
No.
Then why did she call me to say it?
She misunderstood.
What did she do to make her misunderstand?
Nothing.
Just...
Just follow her.
Is it follow or stalk?
What do you mean?
Is there a difference?
Of course there is.
Follow is just right.
Stalk is...
I don't understand.
You don't understand?
What?
Follow.
Are you okay?
What do you want?
You must regret that you want to apologize to her.
Don't forget the soup.
She let us skip the night.
It's a week.
A week?
Don't mind it.
I just skipped one.
At least we don't owe each other.
I don't want to get back with her.
But she's still worried.
She's afraid you'll get into trouble.
So she told her to make it clear.
You guys are even.
It's fine.
Why do you want Hao to tell her?
Just tell her.
You're not on the same team.
Hao won't believe it if you tell him.
It's better to be so exaggerated.
Believe it or not, it's up to him.
No.
I think you should tell her yourself.
It's easier for you to accept it, right?
But it'sосьf breath, right?
Whatever it takes, you have to accept it.
Come on, let's go.
Then we shall see.
Get some clothes.
Do you feel like your heart is about to jump out?
No, it's more like...
Don't stop! Don't stop! Don't stop!
That kind of feeling.
Boss, I want four red beans.
Four red beans?
I want...
Boss, wait!
Two red beans and two cream.
Enough already.
Boss, four cream, thank you.
Four cream.
Two?
Both cream.
You're so fast.
No, no.
Are you sure?
Thank you, Boss.
Er Lian,
are you nervous when you see me?
Why would I be nervous when I see you?
But I am.
Every time I think of him,
I feel like I'm in his arms.
Okay.
Boss, thank you.
Thank you.
Thank you, Boss.
Look at his long eyelashes.
His soft lips. I want to...
So juicy.
Are you too narcissistic?
You're not talking about me.
Then who are you talking about?
Hey, who are you talking about?
Yu Shi Gu.
Yu Shi Gu?
Don't bother me.
That Yu Shi Gu.
I want him.
I really think he's good-looking.
And when I see him, I don't know why my heart...
almost fell out.
Don't turn me around.
I didn't.
At first, it was because
he cried and I felt sorry for him when I saw him.
So I thought I was sympathizing with him,
but that's not what I was thinking.
I noticed that I started to notice him.
When he was studying,
when he was smiling,
when he was walking,
even when he was just standing still,
I couldn't help but look at him.
Even in the infirmary today,
I kept staring at him.
I didn't know what I was doing.
I just felt that he...
He's so cute.
He's really cute.
You like Yu Shi Gu?
Me?
But he's a guy.
What?
You like guys. Tell me.
What's the difference between a guy and a girl?
You're like a girl.
You're the same.
So I like Yu Shi Gu?
Why are you asking me?
You should ask yourself.
I don't want to ask you. I don't know.
I don't know either.
If not, how did you know that you like Li Si Yu?
Li Si Yu is...
I kissed him and then I kissed him.
Then he...
Kissed him and then he...
You're a beast.
I know.
I don't want to.
You're a piece of shit.
Didn't the weather forecast say it would rain?
Where's your umbrella?
You didn't bring it.
Thanks.
Love you.
Okay.
If my parents ask you,
you have to cover me.
Is that really okay?
It is.
You really want to go to the hot spring with Mr. Xiang?
Two days and one night.
Anyway, he's going to choose a car ticket.
Is that right, baby?
What are you doing?
This is a nightclub.
But why would he go to a nightclub?
What else can he do?
He's a good student.
But he's a playboy.
How is that possible?
Baby Yu is very quiet.
He's not the kind of person who can play.
There are many people who are different.
Who knows what he's like in private?
This nightclub is quite special.
It's like the kind of place boys go to.
Oh my god!
It's like a boy is screaming.
What are you doing?
Baby Yu.
Working for 2000 yuan a month.
I have to avoid the school schedule.
Just 10 times.
10 times is enough.
He's a very good student.
What are you doing?
I don't want trouble anymore.
Really?
I'm not.
I need you to confirm something.
I don't want to.
What is there to confirm?
After I'm sure,
I'll tell you.
I've been thinking about you.
I don't know.
Walking, eating, taking a shower,
playing games, even sleeping,
I can see you.
Are you okay?
It's fast.
It's true.
I like you.
What are you doing?
I'm not.
What do you mean?
What?
Does anyone know what a Wasteful World is?
You're fired.
Yu Shi Gu.
What is it?
I don't know.
Be quiet.
You really don't know about the Wasteful World?
Do you know?
Cancel the copyright of the copyrighted books
and the people's clothes.
What about the rights of the people and the rights of the people?
The rights of the people and the rights of the people.
Sit down.
Yes.
Focus.
Others, go in and read the textbook.
Thirdly,
Economic Reform, as I said, is very important.
To abolish the trade system and the right of the nobility,
encourage free trade,
encourage the common people to be free of trade.
This exam must be taken.
Did you hear that?
Write it down.
I don't want to repeat it again.
I'm sorry.
I'll help you stand in the bed.
You don't have both.
I'm sorry.
You eat something before you go to bed?
Come here.
I don't get it.
You look so thin.
Why do you want to lose weight?
Don't worry.
The way I chase after my girlfriend is always...
You don't have one?
I mean what happened between 처리 disappearance...
Then
never mind
You will feel it
Don't make me talk nonsense
What're you gonna do?
I really want to chase you.
Are you a man or not?
I already want to apologize.
Can you be more straightforward?
I'm very straightforward.
I just want to chase you.
I'm sorry.